  <releases>
    <release version="1.3.2" date="2026-07-13">
      <description>
        <p>Update the Flatpak runtime to GNOME 50 and pin release workflow actions to immutable commits.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.3.1" date="2026-07-08">
      <description>
        <p>Show the player window again when media becomes available without triggering an application-ready notification.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.3.0" date="2026-07-04">
      <description>
        <p>Add an optional album artwork color tint for the player window.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.2" date="2026-07-02">
      <description>
        <p>Make the status indicator show and hide actions reliable across Wayland and X11.</p>
        <p>Prevent status indicator menu actions from being activated twice.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.1" date="2026-06-26">
      <description>
        <p>Add compact mode to the status indicator menu.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.0" date="2026-06-24">
      <description>
        <p>Add an optional native status indicator when the desktop supports StatusNotifierItem.</p>
        <p>Add a status indicator menu with show, hide, settings, about, and quit actions.</p>
        <p>Add a preference to disable the status indicator and show when the desktop does not support it.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.1" date="2026-06-24">
      <description>
        <p>Reuse the About dialog on repeated activations without constraining it to the mini-player window.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.0" date="2026-06-24">
      <description>
        <p>Add a header-bar About button and improve About dialog sizing.</p>
        <p>Document the build-tree run command with Meson's development environment.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2026-06-23">
      <description>
        <p>Add release packaging, icon integration, and validator-clean AppStream metadata.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.2.0" date="2026-06-21">
      <description>
        <p>Add background operation, automatic window visibility, preferences, and start-on-login support.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.1.0" date="2026-06-20">
      <description>
        <p>Initial development release.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
